quag.com 2014-05-24

# Privacy | Quag Data Protection Policy Statement

## Privacy

### Quag - Data Protection Policy Statement

#### Company Information

The services mentioned and described in this document are made available and provided by Quentral Srl (hereinafter Quentral), with registered office in Via Durini, 27, 20122 Milan (MI) - VAT no.: 06383360960, registered with Companies House of the Chamber of Commerce of Milan no. REA 1888893, the owner of the web application and Quag.com brand and Controller of the personal data provided by users of Quag.com.

For any questions regarding these data protection regulations, users may send an e-mail to the following address: [privacy@quag.com](mailto:privacy@quag.com)

#### Intent and purpose of data processing

Defined in this statement are the criteria and procedures used by Quentral for processing the personal data provided upon registration with Quag.com and/or published on Quag.com by registered users.

Processing of personal data, in accordance with art. 4, letter a) of Legislative Decree 196/2003, is defined as any operation or set of operations concerning the registration, organisation, storage, consultation, processing, modification, selection, extraction, comparison, use, interconnection, blocking, communication, transmission, cancellation and destruction of personal data.

Therefore, in this section, Quentral intends to illustrate the ways in which the information provided by users when registering and creating their profile on Quag.com will be collected and used, as well as any other information that Quentral acquires as a result of use of the service by all users, both registered and public. Public users are defined as those users who have not yet registered their profile, but who may nonetheless use some of the functions of the application, such as, for example, the search function.

The information provided by users, such as the information required for the registration of a Quag.com account, may be used by Quentral to improve the user experience, for example, by allowing users to receive e-mail notifications regarding the Quag.com service.

We invite all users to read the detailed Statement that follows. In order to complete the registration process on Quag.com and to use the services offered to registered users, said users must give their consent to the processing of their personal data, pursuant to Legislative Decree no. 196/2003.

Users give their consent by creating an account and/or by accessing the site. We nonetheless urge users to carefully read this document and the documents relating to the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Service.

After completing the registration process on Quag.com, registered users may access Member Services and publish content within their personal online profile (including, but not limited to, images, a list of their interests, their gender, nationality, etc.). Such content shall be added voluntarily and at the sole discretion of users, based on their own personal choices and under their exclusive responsibility.

We also wish to inform users – inviting them to take due account of this aspect before making any decision regarding the following – that, by publishing content on the website, they may, even unconsciously provide and disclose additional personal information. The publication of said content (and any personal information that may result or emerge from this content, directly or indirectly) is, in any case, a personal choice freely made by users, entirely of their own volition, with regard to which Quentral is totally extraneous and for which it declines all liability; such choices are made exclusively under the personal responsibility of the user concerned.

#### Data collected

Upon registration, Quag.com asks users for their personal and identification data, i.e. e-mail address and a password that will become the password to access the service; we remind users that they can also register with Quag.com using their facebook, twitter and/or Google+ profile. By clicking on one of the buttons linked to the social networks in the registration/access window of Quag.com, users will be redirected to the login page of the selected social network, through which, after entering the proper credentials, they will be registered automatically on Quag.com. The registration process cannot be completed without this information and thus users will not be able to become registered users of Quag.com, and it will not be possible for them to use the services Quag.com reserves for its members (for more details about Quag.com services, we recommend reading the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Service).

As part of providing its service, Quentral also collects information on which and how services are used by its users, both registered and public (not registered).

This information includes:

    1. **Information on the device used:** 1\. we may collect specific information about the devices used by users to connect to the Quag.com service, (e.g. hardware model, type and version, operating system, browser type and language setting).

    2. **Log information:** the log file is a file in which the actions users make during their Quag.com service session are recorded.When users access our services, we collect and store certain information automatically in server logs. This information includes:

      * Data on how the service is being used, such as search queries, the date and time of requests and the URLs that are part of the Quag.com service, data produced by sessions that use social network functions.

      * The computer's IP address.

      * Information about device events, such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type and language.

    3. **Cookie-based information:** a cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a specific website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognise your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is sent. The risk, however, is that certain services or features of websites may not function properly without cookies.

Within the context of the Quag.com service, cookies are used to manage the sessions of each user, and specifically:  
to perform automatic authentication and to maintain the preferences expressed by users who have logged in to the service, such as those regarding the interface language, search preferences, etc.

**Important:** The history of users' research activity (query history) is not and will never be visible to any other user. This data is strictly confidential and will therefore be protected with the utmost care and attention by the Quag.com service.

#### Use of the data collected

Quentral uses the data collected to enable the registration of users on the Quag.com website, to offer its services, to monitor the use of the website, to test the efficiency of the security procedures, to verify compliance with the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Service, to improve them constantly, and, in this way, to make the users' experience of the service as engaging and enjoyable as possible. All this is carried out while maintaining the protection and privacy of users as our top priority. The information collected by Quentral is used to enable full use of the features and services provided, as well as to provide users with content and information as close as possible to their tastes and preferences. By way of example, by identifying users' areas of interest, it will be possible to contact other users with similar interests.

Advertising and Marketing: Quentral, or subjects authorised thereby, may use the personal data published by users (including the content and information they have contributed) for promotional, advertising and/or marketing purposes, carried out using electronic means such as Internet, the Quag.com website, the social channels of Quag.com (including, but not limited to, Facebook and Twitter), any other social channels identified by Quentral srl and/or e-mail, all in full compliance with the regulations applicable.

For more information, see section  **Information shared by Quentral**  of this document; it is understood that Quentral undertakes never to transfer the personal data of users for marketing or business purposes.

Quentral also enables Quag.com users to interact by sending messages and/or requests for clarification about certain fundamental issues, such as, for example, to report abuse, to report the violation of intellectual property rights, to request clarification on aspects of privacy, etc.

In the event users should wish to contact Quentral, the company itself may retain the contents of any communication sent by users, on the condition that it is useful and/or necessary to provide a better service. In this circumstance, Quentral can also use users' e-mail address to send responses and/or other service-related information.

#### Members and public users, user-shared information

Quag.com is open to everyone and no registration is required. However, user registration and the creation of an account on Quag.com are required to take full advantage of all the features offered by the service.

Users who choose not to register (public users) can take advantage of the search function, but may have limited or no access to some features.

Users who decide to register for the Quag.com service must fill out the registration form, complete with their e-mail address, a user-chosen password to access the application and the name or nickname by which they intend to be recognised by other users within the application. We remind users that the e-mail confirming their registration contains personal information, and as such will never be given to third parties for marketing or commercial purposes.

We remind users, furthermore, that they can also register with Quag.com by using their facebook, twitter and/or Google+ profile. By clicking on one of the buttons linked to the social networks in the registration/access window of Quag.com, users will be redirected to the login page of the selected social network, through which, after entering the proper credentials, users will be registered automatically on Quag.com.

It is important to remember that the information users choose to share publicly may be indexed by other search engines.

Quentral reserves the right to use and exploit all present and/or future applications and/or technologies liable to increase the distribution of the site and its related contents.

#### Quentral's methods of processing personal data

In conformity with the provisions of article 11 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, the personal data of users will be processed lawfully and fairly and will be stored in a form that allows users to be identified for a period of time not exceeding what is necessary for the purposes for which they were collected and subsequently processed. The processing of the personal data of the users will be carried out by electronic means and in the manner prescribed by art. 34 of Legislative Decree 196/2003.

**Personal data and other data identifying the registered user will not be processed for any purpose other than those detailed within this policy statement, and always in full compliance with legal requirements.**

Additional data collected by Quentral, whether from registered or non-registered users, will be processed to meet legal requirements, to improve the Quag.com service and the user experience thereof. We also use this information to provide personalised content, such as for identifying users' areas of interest and helping users to contact others with similar interests, as well as for aggregate statistics of use, which, in any case, will remain anonymous.

**In compliance with the provisions of art.** 31 of Legislative Decree **196/2003** _"Law related to the protection of personal data"_ and further legislation governing the matter, Quentral handles all data collected with full respect for security and privacy. Quentral adopts all the appropriate safety measures to minimise the risks related to destruction or accidental loss of stored data, unauthorised access and any processing that is prohibited or non-compliant with the purposes mentioned above.

In any case, pursuant to art. 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/03, each individual user has the right to obtain information about the collection of data, about the way in which data collection is carried out, the right to request the updating or integration of the data, as well as the right to object to the processing of data concerning him/her.

To exercise these rights, the interested party may submit a request by sending an e-mail to the Data Supervisor at [privacy@quag.com](mailto:privacy@quag.com)

In conformity with the provisions of article 8 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, Quentral will provide users with an appropriate response, without delay, by e-mail. Under article 10 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, if, on the basis of the request described above, the existence of data concerning the applicant is not confirmed, the Data Controller may request the payment of a fee, which may not exceed the actual costs incurred for the research conducted at the user's request.

We remind users that they may view, check and edit all the data they themselves provided at any time, by logging into their profile at [www.quag.com](http://www.quag.com/).

#### Information shared by Quentral

We do not provide personal information to companies, organisations or individuals that are not part of Quentral. 

We provide personal information to organisations and people who are not part of Quentral if we believe, in good faith, that access, use, protection and disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to:

  * Comply with any laws or regulations, legal process or applicable governmental requests.

  * Apply the current Terms and conditions of Use of the Service, including the findings regarding potential violations.

  * Detect, prevent or otherwise manage fraud or security issues or problems of a technical nature.

  * Protect the rights, property or security of Quentral, our users or the public, as required or permitted by law.

#### Other persons in charge of processing

Under articles 4, letters f) and g), 13, letter f), 28 and 29 of Legislative Decree 196/2003, the persons in charge of processing the personal data of Quag.com users are:

1) The Data Controller, responsible for decisions regarding the purposes, the procedures used to process the personal data and the tools used, including the security profile;

2) The Data Supervisors, whom the Data Contollers has specifically appointed to the task of processing personal data.

As already indicated above, the Data Controller is Quentral Srl, with registered office at Via Durini, 27 - 20122 - Milan (MI), Tax Code / VAT No.: 06383360960, registration with Companies House of the Chamber of Commerce of Milan no. REA 1888893.

At the time this statement was issued, other persons responsible for data processing were not mentioned.

#### Storage of data collected by Quentral

**The data that Quentral requests of users for their registration will be stored as long as the relationship between users and Quentral is not ended, for whatever reason.**

Following the logic of maximum transparency, we also wish to point out that even after the relationship with a registered user has ended, Quentral is obliged by law to keep copies of certain data for a certain period of time, in accordance with the provisions of national laws governing the matter (Legislative Decree 109/2008, which amended Legislative Decree 196/2003).

With regard to the storage of other data acquired by Quentral as part of use of the service by registered and non-registered users, the data will be stored by Quentral in an anonymous and aggregate form.

#### Changes

This document may be modified in its entirety on the condition that prior notice is given to all users on the Quentral home page; users could also be informed about the changes by e-mail or with a private message sent by the messaging system integrated into Quag.com. Changes may become necessary due to legal and/or administrative requirements, to upgrade the policy statement itself or even to amend errors and/or inaccuracies found in it, as well as for other reasons not specified at this time.

In order to complete the registration process, obtain access all the services provided by Quentral and use the website, users will need to give their consent to the processing of personal data in accordance with the conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement and for the purposes of art. 23 of Legislative Decree 196/2003.

To give consent to the processing of personal data in compliance with privacy legislation and, in particular, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, it is sufficient to create a personal account after reading this Privacy Policy Statement and the documents relating to the Terms and conditions of Use of the Service of Quag.com, or simply access the service.

Date of last revision: 11/11/2013
